lifeinahouseoftestosterone.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy

Website:  [www.lifeinahouse.net](http://www.lifeinahouse.net/)

This Privacy Policy sets out how Life in a House uses and protects any information that you give while using our website.

Life in a House is a family and lifestyle blog based in Mechanicsville, Virginia, USA. Life in a House is owned by Kimberly Miller. We understand that you care how your information is used and shared while you are visiting our website. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by our website when you visit either on a desktop or on a mobile device. We also discuss how your information is used, how you can control the collection of your information, the correction and/or deletion of your information.

Your information will not be shared with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

In general, we collect contact information which you willingly provide on our contact form, demographic information such as zip code, preferences, and interests via our third-party advertising and analytic plugins such as StatCounter, Google Analytics, Amazon, Google AdSense, GourmetAds and WordPress and finally other information relevant to customer surveys, offers, contests and giveaways.

## Contact Forms

Life in a House uses contact forms on a variety of pages throughout the website. Your name and email address are the only required information we need to respond to your question or concern, but we also have a field for your website URL or name (if you have one) and a message area where you can share your comment or question for us to respond to.

## Social Networking

If you choose to access, visit and/or use any third-party social networking service that May be integrated with our website, we may receive personally identifiable information about you that you have made available to those services, including information about your contacts on those services.

Your decision to use a social networking service to connect with our website is voluntary. However, you should be comfortable with the information your third-party social networking service may make available to our service by visiting those services and reviewing their privacy policies or modify your privacy settings directly with those services.

## Cookies Information

This website uses cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who May combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they have collected from your use of their services. You consent to our cookies if you continue to use our website.

### General Cookie Introduction

Cookies are small text files that can be used by websites to make a user’s experience more efficient.

The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies, we need your permission.

This site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.

You can at any time change or withdraw your consent from the Cookie Declaration on our website.

Learn more about who we are, how you can contact us and how we process personal data in our Privacy Policy.

### Necessary Cookies

Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.

### Preference Cookies

Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.

### Statistics Cookies

Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.

### Marketing Cookies

Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third-party advertisers.

## Log File Information

Log files are automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, referring or exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and other such information.

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Third-Party Advertisements and Technology

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit Life in a House. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. These third-party advertising companies help us present advertisements on Life in a House that are tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites that you have visited to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other click stream data. The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and we disclaim all liability in connection therewith.

## Comments

When visitors leave comments on Life in a House, we collect the data shown in the comments form, and the visitor’s IP address and browser agent string to help with spam detection and to allow us to know if our visitors are using a mobile device or other means to access Life in a House.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

We use the information you submit (including any personal information) to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of our website. By using our website, you consent to this use and any other use of information identified in this Privacy Policy.

Any information you voluntarily disclose while using our website, such as leaving a comment on our website, becomes available to the public. You should be aware that even if you remove the content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your user content.

By providing Life in a House your email address, you consent to our using the email address to send you service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your email address to send you other messages such as newsletters, changes to features of the website, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by sending an email message to [admin@lifeinahouse.net](mailto:admin@lifeinahouse.net) with the word “No Email – Life in a House” in the subject field. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements or offers.

If you do not wish to receive future newsletters from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the message you receive. Note that you may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as transactional or relationship messages, and/or messages about your account profile.

Life in a House may allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services such as technical maintenance, market research, shopping and other classified ads functionality, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. If you choose to purchase merchandise, products and/or services from us through features of the website, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card or other payment processing, order fulfillment, and address verification. There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the website that may be managed or participated in by third parties. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While we may seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, mobile or other device (including its geographic location) which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to gather broad demographic information, analyze trends, trace users’ movements around the website, and to otherwise administer the website. Geographic location information about you and/or your computer, mobile or other device may specifically be used to show you content and sponsored messaging based on geographic location.

We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any lawful purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers, sponsors, clients and customers.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Life in a House will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others.

Life in a House may share your personally identifiable information or information about your computer or mobile device with our affiliates and third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Life in a House (for instance, on services or databases located with our hosting provider).

Except as otherwise described in the Privacy Policy, Life in a House will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law, regulation or subpoena. Please note that we may not provide notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patters for certain Life in a House services.

Life in a House allows third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on our website. These third-party ad servers/networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

Life in a House doesn’t provide any personally identifiable information to these ad servers/networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Life in a House to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers/networks. This privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers.

Google AdSense – [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=US](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=US)

GourmetAds – <https://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>

Amazon – [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)

Life in a House uses reasonable technical and managerial safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Life in a House and you do so at your own risk. We make all reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems, however, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by a breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a secure unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.

### Compromise of Personal Information

If personal information is compromised because of a breach of security, Life in a House will take reasonable measures to promptly notify you if your information has been compromised.

### Your Choices About Your Personal Information

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information to Life in a House in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you.

### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is important to us, as we are parents ourselves. For that reason, Life in a House does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register or subscribe to our services. If we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the age of 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we have information about someone under the age of 18, please contact us at [admin@lifeinahouse.net](mailto:admin@lifeinahouse.net).

### Third Parties

Life in a House expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Third parties including our partners, advertisers, affiliate programs and other content providers accessible through our website may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. If you voluntarily disclose information (including personally identifiable information) in comment areas that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and outside the scope of this Privacy Policy.

### Websites Linked to or From Life in a House

Life in a House is not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from its website nor the information or content they contain. We accept no responsibility for events experienced by you if you visit a third-party site by clicking through from Life in a House to another website. When you click through to visit another website, this Privacy Policy his no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that other websites own rules and policies. It is your responsibility to read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## How to Contact Life in a House

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of Life in a House or your dealing with Life in a House, please contact us at [admin@lifeinahouse.net](mailto:admin@lifeinahouse.net) or send US postal mail to:

Kimberly Miller  
7187 Garden Park Lane #103  
Mechanicsville, VA 23111

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

We thank you for taking the time to update your settings and to read through our Privacy Policy to learn how we manage and protect your data. This Privacy Policy was updated as of May 25, 2018.
